.
I'll be back soon.
You're all gonna pay.
Now that's what I call a torch.
Genius.
Somebody save me.
Let your warm hands break right through.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting.
Waiting for you.
Ooh.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Stay.
Come on.
Election of prom royalty is an archaic and elitist ritual whose time has come.
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
I'm pretty sure this is the last one.
Come on.
Well, we're definitely not done.
I can't wait to see the next one.
Come on.
This is hilarious.
This is a thing I've never done before.
I've never done this before.
It's a ritual whose time has come and gone.
Chloe Sullivan strikes again.
What?
Oh, please don't tell me I lost you to tiara fever, too.
No.
But balloons and taffeta seem a little harmless compared to your usual targets.
Well, this is how I see it.
Homecoming is for jocks, graduations for parents, and prom is the rite of passage that's for
all of us.
It's supposed to be a culmination of four years of memories.
Why do we have to ruin it with the pinnacle of a popularity contest?
a four years of memories.
Why do we have to ruin it
with the pinnacle of a popularity contest?
So, does that mean I order more pizza
for the Brad Pitt marathon?
What? You're not going? What happened with Jason?
Showing up with the coach that got fired for dating a student.
That is an entrance I could live without.
Right.
Besides, after imagining something for four years,
I just don't think it could live up to expectations.
Well, not if you're part of the half-empty persuasion.
And the Lana Aineal wouldn't cop out like that.
Come on, Lana, it's gonna be so much fun.
Lex even got Lifehouse to play for the seniors.
You can help me bring Stag back in style.
Excuse me, coming through.
Smells like school spirit.
Chloe, you may think bashing a sacred school tradition
in your tabloid rag is cool,
but I think it's disgusting.
Lighten up, Dawn.
You'll get your throne because this entire school
is terrified of you and your vicious rumor mill.
Kill me now?
You are such the Hippocrat.
Hippoc...
I'm sorry, whatever it is that you're saying to me
is getting lost in translation.
Don't play stupid.
The only reason your picture's on that wall
is because of your lame article.
What picture?
What wall?
I would say may the best girl win.
But I think we both know who that is.
Laters.
So apparently I'm not the only one
who enjoyed your article.
Your highness.
Good luck.
Who found her?
Gardner.
She's digging a drainage ditch.
Guy's pretty shaken up.
How is her life, sir?
Oh, definitely a total mess.
Too silly to dream of.
So I'm adrift.
No one has done anything.
I must say, you have very different objectives.
You have all your problems in mind.
Chances are you and Lisa are already вообще
on the wrong road.
How are you about that Anita?
Who do you think is on the wrong path, sir?
I think I'm scrapey as a preppy.
enforcing hierarchy Peace Where
Bridget Crosby.
I know that name.
I've come across it several times in my research.
She works for Virgil Swan, the billionaire.
Look, this doesn't concern you.
If it has anything to do with the artifacts, it concerns me.
Edwards, Lally, will you please escort Mr. Teague to his car?
Now, should I bow to you when I see you, or...?
Cute. Very cute.
What about boycotting the boat didn't anyone understand?
Oh, they understand it perfectly.
You see, you are the boycott.
I mean, think about it.
For the last four years, everybody's been trying to break out of the stereotype they've been stuck in.
You're the battle cry.
Ah, the great Smallville High prom coup, huh?
Clark, you didn't happen to have anything to do with this, did you?
I may have spoken to a few people.
Now, I know you're not going to let me storm this best steal alone,
so who is Smallville's most eligible bachelor taking to prom?
I was actually thinking of sitting this one out.
What?
Oh, not you, too.
Wait, let me guess.
You spent four years imagining what it would be like,
and you just don't think it's going to live up to your expectations.
Something like that.
So you're going to let me break out of my rut on stage wearing a sash
while you're at home playing the white horse?
What if game for the 900th time?
I never said you were in a rut.
Yeah, but I am.
And I'm not alone.
You know, Clark, in a couple of weeks,
we're going to graduate from this adolescent fantasy,
and we're not going to have a rut to fall back into.
The thing about expectations, Clark,
is they're supposed to drive you to do more with your life,
not stop you from living it.
Personally, I think the future holds a lot more promise for you
than you give it credit.
So, two o'clock is tanning.
Three is nails.
Four is hair.
And the limo picks us up at six.
If I were you, I'd be more concerned about 12 o'clock.
We don't need to start that early.
No, Dawn, 12 o'clock.
Billy.
Is that your boyfriend crushing on a freshman?
She is so not making pep squad.
First off, wonder bra.
Laters.
The talent.
Hi.
Can you say more?
Mortified?
I mean, prom is only 27 hours away.
Yeah.
How about that?
I'm not going.
Don't be stupid.
Dawn, it's over.
What?
It should have been over a long time ago.
I'm not hanging around just so that I can be a bow tie
that matches your dress.
You can't break up with me the day before prom.
It's over.
Billy!
That's harsh.
Forget it.
It's so yesterday's mystery meet.
Okay.
Massive re-strategy.
I can't go to prom alone.
I need my king.
Get me a yearbook.
I need a yearbook.
I need some of this.
Genius.
You can make me on an airplane.
Harmony, check out this profile.
Okay.
Gorgeous.
Captain of the football team and single long enough
that I'm not sloppy seconds.
Mm-hmm.
Give me the digits for Clark Kent.
Uh-huh.
I waited.
Yeah.
For you.
Don't keep me waiting.
Hi!
Hi.
I feel safe.
Stop! Please! Stop!
Wait! Stop!
Stop!
Holy crap.
I'm Clark Kent's mom.
Mom?
What's going on?
Hi, son.
What's for dinner?
Dinner?
Oh, right.
Here, start with this. It's really yummy.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm great.
I was wanting to ask you,
do you have a date for the prom yet?
Mom, I told you I'm not going to the prom.
What?
You have to go!
No!
Well, I...
I kind of wanted to go with Lana, but it's not...
Lana Lang!
You can't be serious.
You two are so last year.
Clark, your prom is the most memorable night of your life.
I am not going to let you miss it.
You can take me.
Mom, you're already going, remember?
With Dad, you're chaperones.
Oh. Yeah, right. Cool.
Whoosh!
She's gonna do it.
I swear the dog knows I'm allergic.
He follows me around wherever I go.
He's torturing me.
So, this is your little secret.
You're taking her to the prom, aren't you?
Lois?
Mrs. Kent?
A lot of things are possible in this world,
but there will be a man on Mars before Clark and I go to a prom together.
So what, you two just get together in Mac,
but keep it on the down low, in public?
Mom...
I don't mean to be rude, Mrs. Kent,
Mrs. Kent, but did you crack open the cooking sherry?
Of course not. I'm just super pumped about prom.
Well, I'm gonna go.
Mom, maybe I should take you to the Talon tonight.
The Talon? Oh, right. I work there.
Um, no, I can drive myself. Laters.
Laters?
Saw you at a party tonight
I'm psyched Billy dumped Don.
She was getting so stuck up.
I heard he already hooked up with Sue Ann Gardner.
Oh. Sue Ann Gardner is a big fat hoe.
Mrs. Kent?
Oh. Hi, Lana.
Shouldn't you be at school helping with the decorations?
The prom committee needs all the help they can get.
I'm not gonna go to the prom.
Why? You think you're so above it all?
No, of course not.
Oh, come on.
Poor little orphan girl.
Going off to your fancy French art school.
Going out with that big college guy.
I don't have to listen to this.
Hey.
Ow.
Give me my bag, I don't wanna miss my birthday.
Get our flowers.
Why don't people just go home and rent Sophieblossoms again?
You're turnin' up my Tax Affair menu, wifi号.
Bill, rollercoasters are going up.
We Büms and George Marist.
Oh, Jesus.
Green.
Lohot V dont give a fuck.
Oh, you don't wanna promise me that.
Lana, what about Jason?
Clark, it's you I want to go with.
Don't you want to go with me?
Well, I mean, I...
Awesome! It's a date.
I've got to get back to the school and help set up.
They're lost without me.
Laters.
Mom.
Mom, are you all right?
With a life in me, I can't remember how I got here.
Hey.
Hi.
What do you need me to do?
Looking great, guys.
That's perfect.
But remember to use enough tape, okay?
Too much is always better than not enough.
Okay.
Give me that.
Harmony, this is supposed to be cotton candy pink.
Why is it seafoam green?
Nice Don Stiles impersonation.
Yeah, you have the queen bitch control freak down pat.
What's that supposed to mean?
Where is Don anyway?
I have no clue.
And honestly, we'll get way more done without her ordering us around.
See you guys tomorrow.
All right, guys.
Yeah.
Bitch.
All right, so I'll see you guys tomorrow.
All right.
You.
You worked up quite a sweat.
Hey, Lana.
I didn't expect to see you decorating for the prom.
Well, maybe there's more to me than meets the eye.
Heard you got over Don Stiles pretty quick.
I couldn't stand to spend another second with her.
I mean, her voice.
It's a little too nails on a chalkboard.
You know what I mean?
No!
I don't know what you mean!
I don't know what you mean.
But I have an idea.
Why don't you go clean up, and then we can hang out and get to know each other better?
I'll be right back.
Chloe, have you seen Lana?
The only people here are the school spirit club
spreading their prom-aganda.
Why?
There's something going on.
My mom started to act strange.
It's like she's channeling some inner teenager,
and now Lana's not acting like herself.
Well, if you think Lana's here decorating for the prom,
that definitely falls under altered states.
Lana.
What are you doing in here?
Nobody breaks up with Dawn Stiles.
Clark?
Lana?
What's going on?
I don't know.
You came out of the boys' room.
Oh.
Lana, you were just in there.
I don't even know how I got to school.
So do we.
That was Clark.
He's at the hospital.
Billy's going to make a full recovery.
Good.
Clark said he saw me come out of that locker room.
Do you think I could have done anything
when I was blacked out?
Why would I ever hurt Billy Durden?
You wouldn't.
She won't.
But Dawn Stiles would.
Dawn, the girl most likely to be prom queen?
People were saying that you were acting freakishly like her,
and Clark's mom was acting very Dawn-ish
before she came back online at the Talon.
That's the last thing I remember before blacking out,
talking to Martha Kent in the Talon.
And Mrs. Kent says the last thing she remembers
is driving along Route 54.
That's where they found Dawn's body
at the bottom of Carlton Gorge.
The motherlode of all meteor rock.
Oh, my God.
They have her in the emergency room.
She's in a deep coma.
So you think that her spirit was somehow able
to take over Martha and then transfer into me?
Well, we are in Smallville.
And I mean, what would the senior prom be
without a body-snatching prom queen?
Mom, are you okay?
Yeah, I just feel really horrible.
I have no idea what I did.
Well, you didn't do anything.
You were inhabited by Dawn Stiles.
Well, the question is,
now that we have the old Lana back,
where's the new Dawn?
How is she?
Well, she's barely hanging on.
She's got massive head injuries,
and she's severely disfigured.
Disfigured?
No, it couldn't be.
That face was so perfect.
BERNADO
I'm terrified to even think
what else I could have said or done during that last hour.
I'm terrified to even think what else I could have said or done during that last hour.
You just, um, asked me to prom.
Oh. Really?
It wasn't you, though, right? It was Dawn, so...
Code blue, room 256.
Excuse me, are you friends of Dawn's?
Yes. What happened?
There's nothing they can do. I'm afraid she passed on.
I'm sure she didn't suffer.
I'm sorry.
Genius.
You find anything interesting?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I did.
You've crossed the line, Jason.
I take my privacy very seriously.
And I take murder very seriously.
It says here that you sent an e-mail to Bridget Crosby.
I never denied I knew her.
Confirming a meeting between the two of you here at the Luther Mansion
on the same morning she was found face down in the dirt.
Well, Miss Crosby never showed up for that meeting.
You mentioned an item in your email.
I assume you're talking about an artifact.
What are you gonna do? You gonna buy it from her?
Or you gonna take it with force?
I don't need to explain myself to you, Jason.
No, but you're gonna have to explain it to the police.
Look, I have no interest being in the middle of a murder investigation.
I have nothing to do with it.
Not to mention the media circus that comes with it.
There's a dead body found on your property, Lex.
It's kind of hard to ignore.
Trust me, I'm not.
Who are you trying to protect?
You? Your father?
Burying bodies in the backyard isn't exactly a hobby of mine, Jason.
Yeah, well, covering up a homicide isn't exactly a hobby of mine.
I think I'll go have a chat with the sheriff.
I'll be right back.
I just went to see the allergist.
This says I owe $200.
Actually, it's $215, including lab fees.
But all they did was stick a bunch of needles in my back and make me really itchy.
What's that all about?
They need to find out what you're allergic to.
I know what I'm allergic to.
I know what you're allergic to.
He's got four legs and drools.
What I need is a prescription.
Please.
A dog's life depends on it.
Miss?
Maybe I can help you.
Hey, you guys look great.
Clark, the only reason we agreed to be chaperones was because of you.
I know. It's a little backwards.
My parents are going to the prom, and I'm staying home to wait up for them.
Son, when you're older, we don't want you to have to look back on high school and regret not going to the prom.
Dad, I'm not sure that standing by the punch bowl and watching bad dancing is a memory I'm gonna cherish.
I wouldn't be so sure about that, Clark.
That's good.
All right, I'll bring the truck around.
I think I know why you're not going tonight.
When I was a freshman, I remember standing outside and watching the seniors going into prom.
The guys in their tuxes and the girls in their dresses.
I guess I always thought that that would be Lana and me.
Oh, Clark.
Things don't always end up the way you picture them, but sometimes they can end up even better if you give them a chance.
If you change your mind, I put your tux by the door.
You rented me a tux?
Just in case.
Mom.
Well?
How do I look?
Looks like you're going to the prom.
I am.
And you're taking me.
I'm not going to let you sit around moping all night while your parents go out and do the electric boogaloo all night.
It's going to be fun.
No, I'm not going.
Massive free strategy.
You're going to your senior prom whether you like it or not.
End of discussion.
Put on your tux.
Lois, wasn't this not in the realm of possibilities?
Anything's possible, Clark.
Anything.
For me.
Here, Sheriff.
Wait a second.
The body was right here.
It was right next to this rock.
They must have just built this gazebo.
Well, according to the county records,
the gazebo has been here since before the Luthers even heard of Smallville.
Sheriff, I know what I saw.
Uh huh.
The dead and decaying body of one Bridget Crosby.
Mr. Tig, I'll level with you.
Murder mystery is just the kind of thing I could use right about now.
The thing is, you can't have a murder without a victim.
And see, this Bridget Crosby, there's no record that she ever existed.
This is crazy. Of course she existed.
Well, every government database from the IRS to the PTA happens to disagree with you.
I even went on one of those Google searches.
It kept asking me if I meant Bing Crosby.
The gardener. The gardener found the body. Did you question him?
I've questioned the entire housekeeping staff.
It's Lex. He's paid them off, or he's intimidating them.
Or you're yanking my rope.
Mr. Teague, the next time you say there's been a killing, I better see a stiff.
Hello, Mother.
Oh, it's Don.
Lex took care of the body just like we wanted.
Mm-hmm. I love you, too.
I love you, too.
Oh, aren't you so glad you came, Clark? We are going to have so much fun.
Okay, Lois, you got me here. You can stop playing at all.
I'm going to go get some punch.
Come on, Claude. You can do this.
Hey. Haven't I seen you here before?
Well, maybe this time we won't have any natural disasters.
I'm really surprised that you made it.
Yeah, well, remember all those regrets that we were talking about?
I think not seeing you with a crown on your head would be the top of the list.
I'm glad you're here.
Clark! Clark!
It's called an escort for a reason.
And you're here.
In pink. Why?
I came to cheer you on, of course.
Excuse me, everybody. Excuse me.
Thanks, guys.
If I could just get your attention for a moment.
Thank you.
It is time for the big announcement.
Okay, if by some weird reason I win, the tiara-burning party's in my house.
Let's get closer.
You voted, and the results are in.
This year's Smallville High prom queen is...
Chloe Sullivan!
Come on up here, Chloe. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Come on.
What the hell am I doing in a dress? And what the hell am I doing at your prom?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Did you pin that on me?
I'll explain later, Melissa.
I mean...
It goes to the boob, don't you think?
Oh, my God, you guys! Thank you so much!
This is so totally awesome!
I guess I could say I've looked to the stars and wished for this moment ever since I was a little girl.
You can dream of standing here your whole life,
but right now looking down on all of you,
I just, this is just so totally genius.
Thank you so much.
Although, I just have to say
that the person who really deserves this honor
is Dawn Stiles.
No, seriously, you guys.
Seriously, she gave so much of herself,
way more than Chloe Sullivan.
Chloe, Chloe, Chloe, Chloe, Chloe, Chloe, Chloe.
Anyway, I promise this will be one night
that I will always remember,
and you will never forget.
Okay, Smallville, I put my heels together three times
and nothing happened.
Better tell me what's going on.
Oh, Mark...
... Dedin to my semble
But he said road is ten miles
I'm just too scared to go
The 21st century in a place like accuracy
about $75,000
If you have on your plate
I hope you find a way
You're running back to me
You're coming around
I'll be there, be there
You know it's over
Start to breathe and fake a smile
Dad?
Dad, are you okay?
Yeah, it's Chloe.
She's not acting like herself.
She took off down the stairs. I'm fine.
Dad, I need you to get something for me.
Get something from
You're all going to pay.
Get it.
Now that's what I call a torch.
Jeez.
How did you do that?
I know it's you, Dawn.
You don't want to do this.
All those years I kept trying to be what everyone else wanted.
And it turns out those losers don't even care.
This was supposed to be the best night of my life, and they laughed at me.
Let Chloe go.
I will.
See, Clark, there's a whole life after high school.
And I can be whoever I want.
Clark?
The crown's mine, bitch.
Genius.
Don!
Seriously, Mr. Kent.
You can't stop me.
That may be true, but I can stop my son.
What are you doing?
What is that?
It's time for you to leave, Dawn.
Don!
...
Chloe.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
I think you dropped something.
Congratulations, Chloe.
Listen, Lois.
Your parents filled me in.
Apparently some girl named Dawn was possessing me.
Yeah, well, that's the short version.
Yeah, well, it's the last time I let her do my hair.
Look, I'm sorry you got pulled into all this.
Don't worry about it.
I never quite made it to my senior prom.
The punch could use a little kick.
I'm sorry.
You know, I was thinking since you did get all dressed up and you came here with me...
You should at least get a dance out of it.
Chivalry noted.
But I'm not the one you want to dance with, Clark.
Cheers.
Go ahead, Li.
Cheers, aYA.
Cheers.
Com tutti.
solely
da
vermo
music
gases
storm
Hey.
You know, a year from now,
this is all gonna feel like a lifetime ago.
It's funny, because it feels like just yesterday
when you deserted that nervous freshman on the dance floor.
You're headed for Metropolis.
You are destined to be a big-shot reporter at the Daily Planet.
Do you really picture Clark Kent being able to keep up with you?
You know, Lois, I think Clark might have a lot more to offer than you realize.
I wouldn't bet on it.
May I have this dance?
Thought you'd never ask.
I'm going to go give him a kiss.
This is having so much sleight of hand the last few weeks.
The Dick W têm the listened,
and the baby Walter played with Liberty Brothers,
and rapint And then that was me and Ted.
After a few nights involved in head skin te rehabilitation sessions and any outing of late500,
It was an constru of ciao and David.
Nothing I've proven, it's you and me
And I love people and I don't know why
I can't keep my eyes off of you
There's something about you now
I can't quite figure out
Everything she does is beautiful
Everything she does is right
Cause it's you and me
And all other people
Nothing to do, nothing to lose
And it's you and me
And all other people
And I don't know why
I can't keep my eyes off of you and me
And all other people
Nothing to do, nothing to prove
And it's you and me
And all other people
And I don't know why
I can't keep my eyes off of you
It's you and me
There's something about you
And I know nobody comes to take your heart
I know nobody comes to care for you
You don't know why
I'm different when we face each other
And I know nobody comes to control you
Not caring that you were hurt
I know nobody comes to't make you not sad
I can find the things to do
And I know everything that you do
I know everything about you
Always having a best day
So I can't stand at peace
Always having a better day
I know everything about you
I know you're settled
And I know everything about you
I know everything about you
I'm sorry.